{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","address":"13600 W McNichols Rd","zipcode":"48235","owner":"EYM King of Michigan LLC","licenseNumber":"077773","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"6/6/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E61000005CE929308CCB54C0E03EA0105A354540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44832","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","inspectionDate":"2019-01-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"141","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44832","inspectionDate":"1/10/2019","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"In the KITCHEN","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"44832","inspectionDate":"1/10/2019","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\r\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\r\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\r\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\r\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\r\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\r\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\r\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\r\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Throughout Facility","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Hands shall be washed with hot water and soap for at least 20 seconds after contamination."}]},{"inspectionid":"44102","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","inspectionDate":"2018-11-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"127","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44102","inspectionDate":"11/15/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"At the Grease build up","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"44102","inspectionDate":"11/15/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"44102","inspectionDate":"11/15/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"43593","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","inspectionDate":"2018-09-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"112","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"42483","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","inspectionDate":"2018-06-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42483","inspectionDate":"6/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) used for nonpotentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"inspectionid":"42483","inspectionDate":"6/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","violationCode":"4-901.11","violationDescription":"After cleaning and SANITIZING, EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS shall be air-dried or used after adequate draining.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Clean equipment and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored/stacked wet","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Completely air dry all items prior to storage/use."},{"inspectionid":"42483","inspectionDate":"6/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"At the Grease build up","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"42483","inspectionDate":"6/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","violationCode":"3-501.11","violationDescription":"Stored frozen FOODS shall be maintained frozen.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Frozen food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not frozen solid","subProblem":"","location":"FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain frozen."},{"inspectionid":"42483","inspectionDate":"6/7/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."}]},{"inspectionid":"39941","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","inspectionDate":"2017-09-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"130","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"39269","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","inspectionDate":"2017-07-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"130","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"38029","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","inspectionDate":"2017-02-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"130","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"36449","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","inspectionDate":"2016-09-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"129","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36449","inspectionDate":"9/14/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"At the Grease build up","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"36449","inspectionDate":"9/14/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/Replace"},{"inspectionid":"36449","inspectionDate":"9/14/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1426","name":"Burger King ","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Near the Three compartment sink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1426"}}